Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XX is arranged in 15 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XX. DEATH BENEFIT DEPARTMENT
  - Sub-Series 229-0. Death Benefit Department
    - General, 1930-1956 (Box 72, Folder 25)
      1930-Dec. 31, 1956.
    - Actuarial Investigations, 1960-1964 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Grand Lodge Claims, 1957-1961 (Box 72, Folder 27)
      July 1957-Dec. 31, 1961.
    - General, 1922-1926 (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Referendum vote certifications, 1931 (Box 72, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 229-1. Death Benefit Department
    - Insurance Plans, 1921-1931 (Box 72, Folder 30)
      1921-22, 1925-26, 1931.
  - Sub-Series 229-2. Death Benefit Department
    - Information, 1922-1942 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 229-3. Death Benefit Department
    - Rules, Regulations, and Forms, 1931-1951 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Rules, Regulations, and Forms, 1922-1930 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 229-4. Death Benefit Department
    - Interpretation, 1922-1935 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Actuarial Investigations, 1943-1953 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 229-5. Death Benefit Department
    - Grand Lodge-Claims, 1952-1957 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      1952-June 1957.
    - Grand Lodge-Claims, 1939-1951 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Grand Lodge-Claims, 1933-1937 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Grand Lodge-Claims, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Grand Lodge-Claims, 1931 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Grand Lodge-Claims, 1930 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Grand Lodge-Claims, 1926-1929 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Grand Lodge-Claims, 1922-1925 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 229-6. Death Benefit Department
    - Certificates, 1930-1934 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Certificates, 1923-1929 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 229-7. Death Benefit Department
    - Applications for Membership, 1924-1941 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 229-8. Death Benefit Department
    - Amendments, 1924-1935 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 229-9. Death Benefit Department
    - Investment of Funds, 1926-1937 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 229-10. Death Benefit Department
    - Change of Beneficiary, 1958 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Change of Beneficiary, 1927-1935 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 229-12. Death Benefit Department
    - Expenses and salary of actuary, 1931-1940 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 229-13. Death Benefit Department
    - Surrender of Certificates, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 229-14. Death Benefit Department
    - Employment of Attorney, 1932-1951 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 229-15. Death Benefit Department
    - Insurance Department State of New York, 1934-1935 (Box 73, Folder 23)